<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Vahid Mokhtari</title>
    <link>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Vahid Mokhtari</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Link to heading I am a Senior Research Engineer at Flanders Make in the Production CoreLab, where I focus on advancing research and innovation in intelligent manufacturing and production systems.&#xA;Previously, I served as a software engineer at OMP, specializing in the development of software solutions for supply chain planning and optimization.&#xA;I earned my Ph.D. in AI Planning and Robotics from IEETA at the University of Aveiro, Portugal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Line Link to heading Automated planning has been a foundational research area within AI since the field’s inception, with researchers continually making significant contributions over decades. Planning is a decision-making technology that involves reasoning based on a predictive model of a system and deciding how and when to act in order to achieve a desired objective. It is a relevant technology for many application areas that need quick, automated and optimal decisions, such as agile manufacturing, agrifood, and logistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can reach out to me through my linkedin profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mokhtarivahid.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>Here is a selection of my publication:&#xA;Yudha Pane, Vahid Mokhtari, Erwin Aertbeliën, Joris De Schutter, and Wilm Decré. 2021. “Autonomous Runtime Composition of Sensor-Based Skills Using Concurrent Task Planning.” IEEE Robotics and Automation Letters 6 (4): 6481–88. https://doi.org/10.1109/LRA.2021.3094498.&#xA;Vahid Mokhtari, Ajay Sathya, Nikolaos Tsiogkas, and Wilm Decré. 2021. “Safe-Planner: A Single-Outcome Replanner for Computing Strong Cyclic Policies in Fully Observable Non-Deterministic Domains.” In Proceedings of the 20th International Conference on Advanced Robotics (ICAR), 974–81.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
